export default Questions= [
  {
    question: 'Q1 : What Does HTML Stand For?',
    options: [
      'Hyper Text Markup Language',
      'Hypers Tool Markup Language',
      'Home Tool Markup Language',
      'How Text Markup Language',
    ],
    ans: 'Hyper Text Markup Language',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q2 : Who is making the Web standards?',
    options: [
      'Mozilla',
      'The World Wide Web Consortium',
      'Google',
      'Microsoft',
    ],
    ans: 'The World Wide Web Consortium',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q3 : What is the latest version of HTML?',
    options: [
      'HTML4',
      'XHTML',
      'HTML5',
      'HTML6',
    ],
    ans: 'HTML5',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q4 : What is the correct HTML element for the largest heading?',
    options: [
      '<h6>',
      '<h1>',
      '<heading>',
      '<head>',
    ],
    ans: '<h1>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q5 : Which HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?',
    options: [
      'class',
      'font',
      'style',
      'styles',
    ],
    ans: 'style',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q6 : Which HTML tag is used to define an internal style sheet?',
    options: [
      '<style>',
      '<script>',
      '<head>',
      '<link>',
    ],
    ans: '<style>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q7 : What is the correct HTML for adding a background color to a web page?',
    options: [
      '<body bg="yellow">',
      '<body style="background-color: yellow;">',
      '<background>yellow</background>',
      '<bgcolor=yellow>',
    ],
    ans: '<body style="background-color: yellow;">',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q8 : What is the correct HTML for making a text input field required?',
    options: [
      '<input type="text" required>',
      '<input type="text" validate>',
      '<input type="text" required="true">',
      '<input type="text" necessary>',
    ],
    ans: '<input type="text" required>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q9 : What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?',
    options: [
      '<a href="http://www.example.com">Example</a>',
      '<hyperlink>http://www.example.com</hyperlink>',
      '<link>http://www.example.com</link>',
      '<url>http://www.example.com</url>',
    ],
    ans: '<a href="http://www.example.com">Example</a>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q10 : What is the correct HTML for inserting an image?',
    options: [
      '<img href="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
      '<image src="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
      '<img src="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
      '<picture href="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
    ],
    ans: '<img src="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
  },
];


// export default Questions = [
//   {
//     question: 'Q1 : What Does HTML Stand For?',
//     options: [
//       'Hyper Text Markup Language',
//       'Hypers Tool Markup Language',
//       'Home Tool Markup Language',
//       'How Text Markup Language',
//     ],
//     ans: 'Hyper Text Markup Language',
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q2 : Who is making the Web standards?',
//     options: [
//       'Mozilla',
//       'The World Wide Web Consortium',
//       'Google',
//       'Microsoft',
//     ],
//     ans: 'Google',
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q1 : What Does HTML Stand For?',
//     options: [
//       'Hyper Text Markup Language',
//       'Hypers Tool Markup Language',
//       'Home Tool Markup Language',
//       'How Text Markup Language',
//     ],
//     ans: 'Hyper Text Markup Language',
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q2 : Who is making the Web standards?',
//     options: [
//       'Mozilla',
//       'The World Wide Web Consortium',
//       'Google',
//       'Microsoft',
//     ],
//     ans: 'Google',
//   },
//   //   {
//   //     question: 'Q3 : Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:',
//   //     option1: 'heading',
//   //     option2: 'heading2',
//   //     option3: "<'h1'>",
//   //     option4: 'heading6',
//   //     ans: 'ans3',
//   //   },
//   //   {
//   //     question:
//   //       'Q4 : What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?',
//   //     option1: "<'br'>",
//   //     option2: 'lb',
//   //     option3: 'break',
//   //     option4: 'bra',
//   //     ans: 'ans1',
//   //   },
//   //   {
//   //     question: 'Q5 : What is the correct HTML for adding a background color?',
//   //     option1: "body bg='yellow'",
//   //     option2: "<'body style='background-color:yellow;''>",
//   //     option3: 'yellow',
//   //     option4: "<'body background-color='yellow''>",
//   //     ans: 'ans2',
//   //   },
//   //   {
//   //     question: 'Q6 : Choose the correct HTML element to define important text:',
//   //     option1: 'i',
//   //     option2: "<'strong'>",
//   //     option3: 'important',
//   //     option4: 'b',
//   //     ans: 'ans2',
//   //   },
//   //   {
//   //     question: 'Q7 : Choose the correct HTML element to define emphasized text:',
//   //     option1: "<'em'>",
//   //     option2: 'i',
//   //     option3: 'italic',
//   //     option4: 'abr',
//   //     ans: 'ans1',
//   //   },
//   //   {
//   //     question: 'Q8 : Which character is used to indicate an end tag?',
//   //     option1: '/',
//   //     option2: '>',
//   //     option3: '*',
//   //     option4: '^',
//   //     ans: 'ans2',
//   //   },
//   //   {
//   //     question: "Q9 : Which of these elements are all <'table'> elements?",
//   //     option1: "<'table'> <'tr'> <'td'>",
//   //     option2: "<'table'> <'td'> <'tr'>",
//   //     option3: "<'table'> <'tr'> <'tt'>",
//   //     option4: "<'thead'> <'body'> <'tt'>",
//   //     ans: 'ans1',
//   //   },
//   //   {
//   //     question: 'Q10 : How can you make a numbered list?',
//   //     option1: "<'dl'>",
//   //     option2: "<'ol'>",
//   //     option3: "<'list'>",
//   //     option4: "<'ul'>",
//   //     ans: 'ans2',
//   //   },
// ];
